Clyde Plasencia

Software Developer

Overview:

With past experience in management and customer service, and with education in software development, I hope to further my knowledge and skills as a developer. What I enjoy the most in a job is working within a close team to find and repair problems, and create new ideas.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES - LIBRARIES - CONCEPTS KNOWN:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ES6, jQuery, Node.js, MySQL, Express.js, MongoDB, NPM Packages, API's, Object Oriented Programming, CRUD methods, and MVC modeling.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Glenwood Springs Subaru – Lead Service Advisor

May 2015 - May 2019

As the Lead Service Advisor in the Service Dept. my duties included being the main point of contact for customers, handle all customer information and work orders, and assist with training new employees. Over my four years I continually held a higher than national average score for customer service, and was awarded by Subaru of America as Service Advisor of the Year in 2017.

South Mouth — Hiring/Training Manager

August 2013 - March 2015

During day to day operations I would supervise shifts, place orders and keep track of inventory, and hire and train new staff members. During my time spent at Glenwood Springs Subaru I consistently held higher KPI's than the national average in customer service.

EDUCATION:

University of Denver - Full Stack Web Development

August 2019 - March 2020